

CONTACT

akcinarruveyda@gmail.com

0539 825 14 99

www.ruveydaakcinar.com

Denizli, Turkey

PERSONAL SKILLS

Responsible, Team Leader, Positive Thinking, Time Controlled, Organized, Disciplined

ACHIEVEMENTS

Efor All Entrepreneurship Competition / Team Pole Star / 1.st

REFERANCE

<u>Merve İşler</u> - Community Leader & Founder @Fornia

<u>Kadir Şahin</u> - Software Developer @Mysoft Dijital Dönüşüm A.Ş

<u>Beyza Sunay Güler</u>- Developer Relations Coordinator @Google

<u>Batuhan Enes Başay</u> - Backend Developer @ Akinon

SKILLS

Programming Languages: NET Core,

C#, Python .

Web Desing: HTML, CSS, JS, Wordpress Graphic Design: Photoshop, Canva Database: MsSql, MySql, Firebase

SOCIAL MEDIA

in <u>ruveydahilalakcinar</u>

ന <u>ruveydaakcinar</u>

<u>RuveydaAkcinar</u>

<u>ruveydahllakcinar</u>

RUVEYDA HİLAL AKÇINAR

Management Information System

ABOUT

I'm Ruveyda Hilal Akçınar. I graduated from Düzce University Management Information Systems department as one of the top 5. I am developing myself in the web field and I want to work in a place where I can bring myself to better places in this field. I also love to learn, research and tell what I know. I have developed many projects using Asp.net Core. I've also created several projects using the framework. I share the source codes of these projects on Github.

Besides developing myself in software, I am also interested in communities. First, I became a member of 1907 University Fenerbahçe Association 1907UNİFEB and a community manager. Then I took part in the Google Developer Student Clubs (GDSC Düzce) community for 2 years as a core team. I am currently an Ambassador at Google Women Techmakers and an organizer in the Google Developers Groups community.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Manager- Coordinator at Association for Computing Machinery Oct 2019 - Oct 2022

Organization and Membership Officer at 1907 University Fenerbahce Association

FEB 2020 - MARCH 2022

Core team at Google DSC Düzce

SEPT 2020 - JUNE 2022

Full Stack Developer Intern at AugeLab R&D Tech. Inc

DEC 2021 - MAY 2022

Core Team at Google Developer Groups

DEC 2021-NOW

Ambassador at Google Women Techmakers

DEC 2021 - NOW

EDUCATION

Undergraduate - Duzce University

2018-2022 - Management Information Systems

CERTIFICATIONS

Dec 2021 - Entrepreneurship For All

Marmara Technocity

May 2021 - Sektörlerde Yapay Zeka

(Bankacılık, İletişim, Kalite Kontrol, Otomotiv ve Sesli Asistan'da yapay zeka)

The Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (IEEE)

Sept 2021-Certificate of Appreciation | 2020-2021 GDSC Core Team

Google Developer Student Clubs

Oct 2021- Info Session

Google Developer Student Clubs